<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Round Timer</string>

    <!-- FirstScreenText -->
    <string name="Round_Min">Round min.</string>
    <string name="Round_Sec">Round sec.</string>
    <string name="Rest_Min">Rest min.</string>
    <string name="Rest_Sec">Rest sec.</string>
    <string name="Number_Of_Rounds">Number of rounds</string>

    <!-- FirstScreenButtonsText -->
    <string name="Ready">"Ready"</string>
    <string name="Clear">"Clear"</string>

    <!-- FiveSecondScreenText -->
    <string name="StartingInString">Starting in:</string>

    <!-- RoundScreenText -->
    <string name="Rest">Rest</string>
    <string name="Round">Round</string>
    <string name="Pause">Pause</string>
    <string name="Resume">Resume</string>
    <string name="Finish">Finish</string>

    <!-- PreviewRoundBoxText -->
    <string name="Rounds">Rounds</string>

    <!-- SaveRoundBannerText -->
    <string name="Saved">Saved</string>

    <!-- SettingsButtonText -->
    <string name="Settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="Tips">Tips</string>
    <string name="About">About</string>

    <!-- AboutScreen -->
    <string name="Version">Version</string>
    <string name="Description">Maximize your workouts with this customizable timer for precision training. Set specific times for active laps and rest intervals, tailored to any exercise routine. Train smarter and more effectively!</string>

    <string name="PrivacyPolicy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="TermsOfService">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="SendFeedback">Send Feedback</string>
    <string name="ContactMe">Contact me:\u00A0</string>

    <!-- Privacy Policy Paragraph -->
    <string name="PrivacyPolicyParagraphTitle">Privacy Policy for RoundTimer</string>
    <string name="PrivacyPolicyParagraph">
        Last Updated: 23/October/2024\n\n
        At RoundTimer, we respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy outlines what information we collect, how we use it, and how we protect your data when you use the RoundTimer application.\n\n
        1. Information We Collect\n
        RoundTimer does not collect any personal information from users. The only information we may access is any data that Google, Samsung Galaxy Store, or F-Droid collect when you download or install the app from their respective platforms. For more details on what these stores collect, please refer to their respective privacy policies:\n\n
        - Google Privacy Policy\n
        - Samsung Privacy Policy\n
        - F-Droid Privacy Policy\n\n
        The only information we receive directly is any data you voluntarily send to us via email at netbug94@gmail.com, such as feedback, bug reports, or support inquiries.\n\n
        2. Use of Information\n
        Since we do not collect any data within the app itself, we do not process or store any personal information. Any information sent via email will only be used to respond to your inquiries or improve the app.\n\n
        3. Third-Party Services\n
        The RoundTimer app does not use any third-party services that collect data directly from the app. However, when downloading the app from the Google Play Store, Samsung Galaxy Store, or F-Droid, the respective store may collect information related to your usage and install. For more details, please refer to the privacy policies of these platforms:\n\n
        - Google Privacy Policy\n
        - Samsung Privacy Policy\n
        - F-Droid Privacy Policy\n\n
        4. Email Communications\n
        If you contact us via email at netbug94@gmail.com, any information you provide in your email (such as your name or email address) will only be used to respond to your questions or improve the app. We do not share this information with any third parties.\n\n
        5. Security\n
        Since RoundTimer does not collect any personal data from users directly, there is minimal risk of data breaches. However, if you contact us via email, we take reasonable precautions to protect the information shared through email communications.\n\n
        6. Changes to This Privacy Policy\n
        We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes will be reflected on this page, and the updated policy will include the effective date of the revision.\n\n
        7. Contact Information\n
        If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at netbug94@gmail.com.
    </string>
    <!-- Terms of Service Paragraph -->
    <string name="TermsOfServiceParagraphTitle">Terms of Service for RoundTimer</string>
    <string name="TermsOfServiceParagraph">Last Updated: 23/October/2024\n\nWelcome to RoundTimer, an open-source timer application. By using this application, you agree to be bound by the following terms and conditions. If you do not agree with these terms, please do not use the app.\n\n
        1. Open-Source Usage\nRoundTimer is provided as open-source software. You are free to use, modify, and distribute this application in accordance with the MIT License. However, commercial use of this app or any of its modifications for profit is strictly prohibited. This means you may not sell the app, any derivative works, or charge for services related to its use.\n\n
        2. Permitted Use\nYou may use this app for any lawful, non-commercial purposes. You may modify the app and redistribute it as long as you follow the terms outlined in the MIT License. Any redistribution of the modified version must include the original copyright notice and this permission notice.\n\n
        3. Disclaimer of Warranties\nThis application is provided "as is" without any warranties or guarantees. Use of this app is at your own risk. The app may not function as expected in all environments, and we are not responsible for any damages, data loss, or issues resulting from the use of the app.\n\n
        4. Limitation of Liability\nUnder no circumstances will the developer of RoundTimer, netbug94, be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, or consequential damages arising from the use or inability to use the app.\n\n
        5. Changes to the Terms\nThese terms may be updated from time to time. Users will be notified of any significant changes, and continued use of the app after such changes will constitute acceptance of the updated terms.\n\n
        6. Contact Information\nIf you have any questions or concerns about these Terms of Service, please contact me at netbug94@gmail.com.
    </string>
    <!-- Send Feedback -->
    <string name="AttachRestrictionMessage">You can only attach up to 2 files.</string>
    <string name="FeedbackSubject">Subject</string>
    <string name="FeedbackMessage">Message</string>
    <string name="AttachmentButtonText">Attach Files (up to 2)</string>
    <string name="FileAttachedText">files attached</string>
    <string name="SendEmailText">Send email…</string>
    <string name="NoEmailMessage">No email client installed.</string>
    <string name="SendButtonText">Send</string>

    <!-- Delete & Cancel -->
    <string name="Delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="Cancel">Cancel</string>

    <!-- Delete Confirmation Dialog and  -->
    <string name="DeleteEntity">Delete Entity</string>
    <string name="AreYouSureString">Are you sure you want to delete</string>

    <!-- WorkoutListScreen -->
    <string name="DeleteSuccessful">Workout deleted successfully</string>
    <string name="EmptyListString">Empty list</string>

    <!-- WorkoutListItem -->
    <string name="TextFieldTitleWorkoutListItem">Name</string>
    <string name="UpdatedSuccessful">Updated successfully</string>
    <string name="CannotBeEmpty">Name cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="RoundTimeString">Round Time</string>
    <string name="RestTimeString">Rest Time</string>

    <!-- SettingsScreen -->
    <string name="TransitionScreenDuration">Transition screen duration</string>
    <string name="VoiceOptionsString">Voice options</string>
    <string name="BeepOptionsString">Beep options</string>

    <!-- TransitionScreenOptionExtensions -->
    <string name="TransitionOptionFiveSeconds">Five second screen</string>
    <string name="TransitionOptionThreeSeconds">Three second screen</string>

    <!-- FirstScreenContent -->
    <string name="EntityFirstWord">Entity</string>

    <!-- VoiceOptionExtensions -->
    <string name="MuteString">Mute</string>
    <string name="WomanVoiceString">Woman </string>
    <string name="ManVoiceString">Man</string>

    <!-- BeepOptionExtensions -->
    <string name="DefaultBeepString">Default beep</string>

    <!-- <string name=></string> -->

</resources>

